https://www.fayfoto.com/about-fayfoto/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Menu HomeAbout FayFotoWhat’s Special About FayFoto Boston?FAQWebsite Privacy PolicyYour PeopleBusiness PortraitTeamsWorkplaceGroupsEventsYour PlacesYour ThingsIndustry and TechnologyContact FayFotoArticles
Menu HomeAbout FayFotoWhat’s Special About FayFoto Boston?FAQWebsite Privacy PolicyYour PeopleBusiness PortraitTeamsWorkplaceGroupsEventsYour PlacesYour ThingsIndustry and TechnologyContact FayFotoArticlesWho we areOur website address is: https://www.fayfoto.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itWe’ll make this brief. With two exceptions (noted below, “Google Analytics” and “Contact Form”) FayFoto Boston does not knowingly or intentionally capture or store any data from visitors to our website.We do not support accounts for users of this website. We do not have comments enabled for blog posts. We do monitor site traffic with Google Analytics.We do use a contact form, and that allows us to continue a conversation initiated by the site visitor. So in that case we assume the writer has given us permission to communicate by email or telephone.We use this information internally and only to interact with a customer or prospect.We do not in any circumstance sell or otherwise distribute any personal information received via an interaction with this website.
Search for:
Recent Posts Oh, hello… Covid-19 Safety Protocol Statement Looking Back During Covid-19 Days Zhoosh Client specifications Getting to “Yes” with a Business Portrait File Size: What website maintainers should ask their website developers Labels, Distinctions, and Discoverability Professionals Do Sweat the Small Stuff Evolving Business Portrait Background Styles Keeping Track of Client Details FayFoto’s Negative Archive now lives at Northeastern University Start Here Evolution: FayFoto’s Transition to Digital Services Managing a Successful Group PhotoElsewhere…Find FayFoto Boston on Facebook and LinkedIn.Find Steve Nelson on LinkedIn, Flickr, and Instagram.FayFoto Boston is a member of the Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce and the Greater Boston Convention and Visitors BureauYou might also enjoy Boston Scenic PhotosBring a flavor of what you love about Boston to your home or office with Fine Art photographic prints of Boston scenes and landmarks. ContactBy Mail: FayFoto Boston 15 Main Street, Suite 241 Watertown, MA 02472By Phone: 617-267-2000By Email: office@fayfoto.com
HomeAbout FayFotoWhat’s Special About FayFoto Boston?FAQWebsite Privacy PolicyYour PeopleBusiness PortraitTeamsWorkplaceGroupsEventsYour PlacesYour ThingsIndustry and TechnologyContact FayFotoArticles
Close
